http://www.mden.com/privacy-policies.html

Privacy Policies
The Internet is an incomparable resource for information, that, now more than ever before, has become an integral part of daily life. However, it is also a means of collecting personal details about you that you may not want to be made public - home address, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, to name a few. Some websites may be gathering this and other information about you without you even knowing about it.
M Den will strive to make your Web surfing as private and secure as possible so that you can have a positive online experience that provides you with all the information you could ever dream of. So, although we do collect user data at times, we want to help ensure that it remains private and secure.
Your Privacy
M Den promises that it will not disclose your personal information to third parties except for trusted third parties with whom we have contracts; and even then, the purpose of the disclosure will be only to help us improve this website and to report about general usage. The information we collect is used for internal review to improve the content of our Web site and to better serve our users. If we choose to disclose personal information, it will be with trustworthy third parties who have been contracted to work with M Den. In such a case, it will be for the sole purpose of providing aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information. These statistics will remain anonymous with no personal identifying information. The M Den may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to:
comply with law,
enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or
protect the rights, property or safety of the website, its users or others.
The M Den will share information with our most important partner, the University of Michigan Athletic Department, so that together The M Den and The Athletic Department can improve the information, products and experiences of all fans through tailored advertising. MDen and the University of Michigan Athletic Department will be doing this through 'cookie tracking' - for more info, please feel free to visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. To opt out of the tracking, if you see an online display banner, please click on the 'ad choices' icon in the corner of the ad and disable.
At the M Den, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to gauge customer satisfaction in order to better serve your wants and needs:
When you order from our e-commerce store, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process your order and ship it as quickly as possible.
When you enter a contest or participate in other promotional features on mden.com, we may ask for your name, phone number, address, e-mail address or additional demographic information so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
We may also use the information we collect from you upon purchase and/or entry to conduct market research surveys and send you marketing communications. This way, M Den can be sure to provide the service and merchandise that our fans are looking for.
Use of IP Address
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by this number.
The M Den collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, reporting aggregate information to advertisers, and auditing the use of our site. When guests request pages from this site, our server logs the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service, or to protect our service, site, customers or others.
Use of Cookies
The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites.
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies.
We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs. By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies.
The M Den has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. For example, our Web sites often include form entries. When entering a contest or sweepstakes, users enter several pieces of personal information. On a subsequent visit, this information may be used to automatically fill in portions of the form, thus saving the user from having to re-enter this information. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of our Web site services that our users find valuable.
Security
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Once we receive your transmission, we use our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. The M Den will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, other than as specifically set forth below, M Den cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or the security of information we or our affiliates transmit to you. You therefore send and receive information to and from mden.com at your own risk. Ultimately, you are responsible for for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.
Your Online Purchasing Security
We guarantee a secure shopping experience. We protect you while you shop for your favorite mden.com merchandise, so you never have to worry about online credit card safety. We guarantee that every transaction you make at mden.com will be risk-free. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at mden.com.
Guarantees
Under the federal law, your credit card issuer cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your credit card issuer does hold you liable for up to $50.00, M Den will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. M Den will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made on mden.com while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
Your Consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by M Den as previously explained. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
